<?xml version="1.0"?> <rss version="2.0"> <channel> <title>Squadron News (WWCO RSS)</title> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/</link> <description>News about The WorldWide CDI Organization.</description> <language>en-us</language> <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2023 16:21:00 GMT</pubDate> <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2023 16:21:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>  <generator>The Sunflower Innovators</generator> <managingEditor>Nicholas Jones</managingEditor>  <item> <title>Meet — M1</title><image> <url>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/wwco-org/w/master/ru/wp-content/themes/shiro/assets/src/png/M1.png</url></image><category>Update, Community, Advocacy</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/4/</link> <description>Meet the M1 Update for all FKAWP Uneditable projects, see what improvements we have made to projects in FKAWP including editable projects</description> <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2023 16:29:21 GMT</pubDate> </item> <item> <title>WorldWide CDI Organization Launches Campaigns for FKAWP Member Projects in the USA</title> <image> <url>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/ru/wp-content/themes/shiro/assets/src/jpg/wwco-usa.jpg?w=800&h=600&crop=1</url></image><category>Community</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/ru/4/index.html</link> <description>This month, the WorldWide CDI Organization, a global non-profit organization that makes knowledge free and available to everyone around the world, is launching a series of campaigns to bring FKAWP member projects to the United States. Articles of all FKAWP projects for readers from the USA and many other countries will have articles in their native language ….</description> <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 11:06:42 GMT</pubDate> </item> <item> <title>The European Parliament and Council are debating amendments to the draft proposal for the Digital Services Act (DSA)</title><image> <url>https://kaz.tengrinews.kz/userdata/news_kk/2020/news_310146/thumb_m/photo_69011.jpeg?w=800&h=600&crop=1</url></image><category>Community, Advocacy, Politics</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/3/index.html</link> <description>WWCO Projects system of open collaboration has enabled knowledge-sharing on a global scale for more than 4 years. It is one of the most beloved websites in the world, as well as one of the most trusted sources for up-to-date knowledge about biology, astronomy, nuclear chemistry and physics, ecology, as well as materials about the Earth planet. All of this is only made possible by laws that protect its volunteer-led model.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 6 Jun 2022 08:37:32 GMT</pubDate> </item> <item> <title>Top reasons to support The WWCO Open Knowledge Projects</title><image> <url>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/ru/wp-content/themes/shiro/assets/src/jpg/nature.jpg?w=800&h=600&crop=1</url></image><category>Community</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/ru/2/index.html</link> <description>In the 4 years that have passed since the inception of the World CDI Organization, it has grown to become a valued and loved learning destination for millions of people around the world. Now with over 60 million contributors and thousands of articles on projects, its growth is supported by a global volunteer force and contributors who regularly review and visit the site….</description> <pubDate>Sun, 1 Jan 2022 08:56:02 GMT</pubDate> </item> <item> <title>How the idea of creating the concept of WWCO and the WorldWide CDI Organization appeared?</title> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/news/ru/1/index.html</link><image> <url>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/ru/wp-content/uploads/sites/25/2021/11/WWCO-Flag.jpg?w=800&h=600&crop=1</url></image><category>Community</category> <description>In such a short period of time, the WorldWide CDI Organization has already become a giant in the field of online education and distribution of free knowledge on the Internet. Free knowledge organizations and projects such as Wikimedia, BRE, Scholarpedia and others create a global community that is constantly growing and evolving….</description> <pubDate>Fri, 7 Jan 2022 18:06:32 GMT</pubDate> </item> <item> <title>WWCO Projects adopts a Universal Code of Conduct Conceived for the new Era of the Internet</title> <image> <url>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/ru/wp-content/themes/shiro/assets/src/png/wwco-projects-logo.png</url></image><category>Uncategorized</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/2021/02/02/wikipedia-embraces-first-of-its-kind-universal-code-of-conduct/index.htm</link> <description>On October 15, the WorldWide CDI Organization, the non-profit organization that manages WWCO projects, launched and adopted the Universal Code of Conduct, which expands on existing project policies to create a universal set of community standards to combat negative online behavior...</description> <pubDate>Sun, 1 Jan 2022 06:53:04 GMT</pubDate> </item><item> <title>How the WorldWide CDI Organization contributes to nature conservation?</title> <image> <url>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/ru/wp-content/uploads/sites/25/2021/01/Wikipedia20_PressReleaseHeader_2.png?w=800&h=430&crop=1</url></image><category>Uncategorized</category> <link>https://wwco-org.github.io/w/en/2021/01/14/SQN/index.htm</link> <description>The WorldWide CDI Organization's products, working methods and relationships with partners are united by one mission of increasing environmental and social responsibility. We systematize information about our planet and create technologies for their practical use. This is how we help people around the world to contribute to the conservation of nature.</description> <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2021 04:56:48 GMT</pubDate> </item></channel> </rss>
